<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This metadata copyright 2019 Todd Warner <t0dd_at_protonmail.com> -->
<!-- https://docs.fedoraproject.org/en-US/packaging-guidelines/AppData/ -->
<!-- https://www.freedesktop.org/software/appstream/docs/chap-Metadata.html -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>joplin.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>Joplin</name>
  <summary>A free and secure notebook application.</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Joplin is a free and secure notebook application. Organization is easy using
notebooks and tags which can all be synchronized between your various devices.
The notes are can be searched, copied, tagged, and modified either from the
applications directly or from your own favorite text editor. The notes are
composed with the ever-popular and familiar markdown format.</p>

    <p>Notes can be imported from Evernote, to include all associated resources
(images, attachments, etc) and all metadata (geo-location, update time,
creation time, etc). Notes can, of course, also be imported from any other
markdown source.</p>

    <p>Mirroring to your devices and redundancy is achieved by a simple, and
optionally encrypted, synchronization to various cloud services including
Nextcloud, Dropbox, Onedrive, WebDAV, or your local or network-accessible file
system.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>For all of your devices</caption>
      <image>https://camo.githubusercontent.com/372ddfe5bb318ccbdd6803a8fec25b642a335a92/68747470733a2f2f6a6f706c696e2e636f7a69632e6e65742f696d616765732f416c6c436c69656e74732e6a7067</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://joplinapp.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/laurent22/joplin/issues</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/taw00/joplin-rpm/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://discourse.joplinapp.org/</url>

  <update_contact>t0dd_at_protonmail.com</update_contact>

  <developer_name>Laurent Cozic</developer_name>

  <provides>
    <binary>joplin-desktop</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.165" date="2019-08-15">
      <description>
        <p>More information here: https://github.com/laurent22/joplin/releases/tag/v1.0.165</p>
        <p>Summary:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>New: Added support for Fountain screenwriting language</li>
            <li>New: Add solarized themes to desktop client (#1733)</li>
            <li>New: Added support for templates (#1647)</li>
            <li>New: Added markup language to property dialog</li>
            <li>New: Add support for cinnamon to install script (#1738)</li>
            <li>Improved: Better handling of adding the title to print and export to PDF (#1744)</li>
            <li>Improved: Improved bold formatting support in Enex import (#1708)</li>
            <li>Improved: Create fileURLs via drag and drop (#1653)</li>
            <li>Improved: No longer crash if certain theme properties are not set</li>
            <li>Improved: Make translation files smaller by not including untranslated strings. Also add percentage translated to config screen. (#1459)</li>
            <li>Improved: Only repeat failed requests up to 3 times during sync</li>
            <li>Improved: Upgraded packages to fix security issue</li>
            <li>Improved: Make depthColor theme property optional</li>
            <li>Improved: Optimised loading of multiple items</li>
            <li>Improved: Disable Markdown actions for HTML notes</li>
            <li>Improved: Footnote, toc-done-right, anchor (#1741)</li>
            <li>...and other fixes and more minor improvements</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Note: Haven't been keeping up with every release in these notes. Apologies. I will probably be lax about it again. -todd</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.140" date="2019-03-10">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes, code refactoring, and performance improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>

